Dave Del Purgatorio

Address: Oakland, CA 94601, United States • Phone number: 510.684.8310
 Email address: delpurg@gmail.com • Web: https://www.linkedin.com/in/davedp/



Profile

Customer-focused and dedicated Help Desk / Technical Support / Systems Administration with 15+ years of experience within the Fintech, Higher Education, SMB and Banking space. Taking ownership of business-problems and addressing them with technology is my passion. Communicating effectively with my colleagues and leading by example has allowed me to partake and deliver great solutions to my current and past employers over the years.



Work experience

05/2018 – 12/2021 Redwood City, California, USA

Lead Senior Enterprise Support WePay

During my 3+ years at WePay, I was the Help Desk Team Lead, helping providing Enterprise-class service to deliver the most value to our end users and customers.

Infrastructure Support:

- Supporting 500+ Mac fleet managed using JAMF DEP/MDM tools for onboarding/offboarding and software/hardware management
- Management of MacOS via JAMF MDM and SSH sessions using bash and zsh
- Help Desk Ticketing and Docucumation using Jira Service Desk and Confluence
- Citrix Workspace VDI Support
- HP Printer Support and management using PaperCut MF
- Google Workspace Administration
- Slack Administration
- Box and Google Drive Administration
- Meraki WiFi Administration and support
- OneLogin Administration for supporting company-wide SAML/OIDCenabled apps
- Active Directory Support of user and group accounts via both GUI and Powershell scripting
- Supporting Druva Cloud Backup/Restore for company MacBook's and enduser Google Drive data
- Supporting end user DUO MFA services
- Supporting Palo Alto Global Connect VPN services
- Supporting Corporate Zoom Rooms and A/V System Services for All-Hands/VIP meetings
- Assisting Network engineering team with Cisco Catalyst Switches for troubleshooting and rectifying layer 1, layer 2 and 802.1x issues

Some accomplishments while working at WePay:

• Implemented Remote Onboarding training/Laptop deployment when



- Covid Lockdown forced our offices to close
- Engineered and deployed a mobile zoom and wireless A/V & PA system for Leadership Team offsite engagements
- Deployment and management of Yubikeys for both IT and DevOps/Engineering teams for use to harden our critical infrastructure all remotely during lockdown
- Deployment of Robin Desk Booking System and Reservation Kiosks for Office seating arrangement for post-lockdown office access

07/2015 - 05/2018 San Francisco Bay Area

Freelance Systems Administration and Desktop/Mobile **Support**

- GCP Google Compute Engine and AWS EC2/LightSail experience
- Working within the Managed Service Provider, Data Analytics, Biopharmaceutical and Auto industries
- Providing Windows 7, 8.1, 10, Windows Server 2008R2, Windows Server 2012R2 rollouts
- Active Directory Administration, Exchange 2010/2013 Administration, vSphere 5.5 and 6.x, Hyper-V 2012R2 Administration
- Supporting iOS and Android mobile devices with Exchange and Mobile Device Management/Enrollment
- Help Desk support using ServiceNow, Jira and ConnectWise PSA's
- Document management supported using Confluence and SharePoint

04/2005 - 07/2015Berkeley, CA

Senior Systems Administrator Graduate Theological Union

- Managed Core Active Directory Infrastructure services (DNS, DHCP, WINS ,Group Policy)
- Windows XP and 7 Desktop Deployments, Imaging and management
- Managed Exchange 2010 Servers and Services
- Managed ShoreTel VoIP phone system
- Managed VMware VSphere 4.1/5.0 Datacenter
- Managed EMC Storage Area Network Infrastructure
- Managed daily Moves/Adds/Changes to security groups and network
- Provided 2nd/3rd tier escalation support to Help Desk

2004 - 2005

Support Engineer GoPrint

Provided on-site and remote system support for GoPrint customers; building, deploying and troubleshooting GoPrint hardware and software



Education

08/1994 - 01/1996San Francisco, USA **Broadcasting and Electronic Communications** San Francisco State University

09/1991 - 06/1994 Pittsburg, CA, USA

Recording Arts Los Medanos College



Jamf Certified Admin
JAMF

 $http://jamf.idworks.com/jamf_certification.php?id=12282\&code=JCA6318AEF$

Credential ID: 201910-37151

• VMware Certified Professional - Data Center Virtualization VMware

Credential ID: VMW-00350300C-00450639

O1/2019 • Apple Certified Macintosh Technician (ACMT)
Apple

Credential ID: 346762335

11/2017 • Apple Certified Associate - Mac Integration Apple

Credential ID: APPL282794